let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Вопрос 1?",
    answer: "Ответ 1",
    options: [
      "Ответ 1",
      "Ответ 2",
      "Ответ 3",
      "Ответ 4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Вопрос 2?",
    answer: "Ответ 2",
    options: [
      "Ответ 2",
      "Ответ 26",
      "Ответ 37",
      "Ответ 48"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Вопрос 3?",
    answer: "Ответ 3",
    options: [
      "Ответ 17",
      "Ответ 25",
      "Ответ 33",
      "Ответ 3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Вопрос 4?",
    answer: "Ответ 4",
    options: [
      "Ответ 4",
      "Ответ 23",
      "Ответ 31",
      "Ответ 48"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Вопрос 5?",
    answer: "Ответ 5",
    options: [
      "Ответ 11",
      "Ответ 25",
      "Ответ 5",
      "Ответ 47"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Вопрос 6?",
    answer: "Ответ 6",
    options: [
      "Ответ 19",
      "Ответ 26",
      "Ответ 37",
      "Ответ 6"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Вопрос 7?",
    answer: "Ответ 7",
    options: [
      "Ответ 15",
      "Ответ 28",
      "Ответ 65",
      "Ответ 7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Вопрос 8?",
    answer: "Ответ 8",
    options: [
      "Ответ 29",
      "Ответ 8",
      "Ответ 77",
      "Ответ 90"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Вопрос 9?",
    answer: "Ответ 9",
    options: [
      "Ответ 189",
      "Ответ 266",
      "Ответ 9",
      "Ответ 610"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Вопрос 10?",
    answer: "Ответ 10",
    options: [
      "Ответ 191",
      "Ответ 267",
      "Ответ 357",
      "Ответ 10"
    ]
  }
];